import 'package:pkk_project/models/question.dart';

const List<Question> questions = [
  Question(
    question: '1. What is the past tense of the verb "eat"?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) eated',
      'b) eat',
      'c) ate',
      'd) eaten',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '2. Which of the following is a modal verb?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) walk',
      'b) can',
      'c) running',
      'd) jumped',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '3. What is the opposite of the adjective "happy"?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) sad',
      'b) angry',
      'c) joyful',
      'd) excited',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '4. Which of the following is a synonym for the word "big"?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'a) small',
      'b) tiny',
      'c) little',
      'd) large',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '5. What is the plural form of the noun "child"?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) childs',
      'b) children',
      'c) childes',
      'd) child',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '6. Which of the following is a preposition?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) jump',
      'b) happy',
      'c) on',
      'd) run',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '7. What is the present participle of the verb "sing"?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) sang',
      'b) singing',
      'c) sings',
      'd) sung',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '8. Which of the following is an adverb?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'a) book',
      'b) quickly',
      'c) table',
      'd) slowly',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question:
    '9. Which of the following is a conjunction?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) and',
      'b) play',
      'c) happy',
      'd) quickly',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question:
    '10. What is the comparative form of the adjective "good"?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) more good',
      'b) goodest',
      'c) better',
      'd) goodlier',
    ],
  ),
];
